http://www.seasky.org/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
Your Internet privacy is very important to us here at Sea and Sky. We take every possible measure to maintain the privacy of visitors and users to this site. Sea and Sky will never collect any personal information such as names, ages, or addresses from any of its users. All information collected by this site consists of anonymous, statistical information only and is used for purely analytical purposes. This information helps us to better understand our audience so we can continually improve the site and make it more useful for our users. We also serve advertisements in order to help pay for our Web hosting and operating costs. These ads may use cookies to provide a customized ad experience for each user.
Information We Collect
What the Information is Used For
Use of Cookies
Outside Parties
Third Party Links
Disabling Cookies
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Your Consent
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Contact
Information We Collect
Sea and Sky collects data on site traffic patterns and statistics to help us better understand our audience. However, no personally identifiable information is collected. This statistical data is used to improve the structure and content of the site to further improve the visitor experience.
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Return
What the Information is Used For
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from our visitors.
To improve customer service. Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
Return
Use of Cookies
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site or service provider systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Return
Outside Parties
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties any personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information and statistics may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Return
Third Party Links
Sea and Sky provides links to external, third party sites as a service to our visitors.
These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use general information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Some advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on this site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information that may include your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit this site, and whether you have Flash installed along with other details.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of these
cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of these
cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
The cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on this site. Third party advertising companies may also collect information about other sites you have visited in order to display advertisements on this site based upon your interests. To view Google's Privacy policy go to: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html
Return
Disabling Cookies
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Return
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Return
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Return
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Return
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Sea and Sky reserves the right to change these policies at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on 7-2-2013
Return
Contact
If you have any further questions regarding the site Privacy Policies of Sea and Sky, please contact us by email.
Return
To search this site, type your search word(s) in the
box below and click the search button:
Home Page | Explore the The Sea | Explore the The Sky
About Sea and Sky | Frequently Asked Questions | Site Map | Awards
Privacy Policy | Contact Sea and Sky
Visit Us on Facebook | Follow Us on Twitter
All content on this site is Copyright © 1998 - 2016 by Sea and Sky. All rights reserved.
Content from this Website may not be used in any form without written permission from the site owner.
Sea and Sky receives commissions for purchases made through links on this site.
Visit Us on Facebook
Follow Us on Twitter
